Guide to the John Nolen Papers,1890-1938, 1954-1960.
Nolen, John papers,1890-1938, 1954-1960.
- Series IV. Professional Career
  - Other Professional Activities, and Public Works
    - Public Lectures Illustrated by Slides
      - Terrace in front of Palace, Budapest, D184 (Box 153)
      - Agricultural Museum, Budapest, D186 (Box 153)
      - Piazza San Marco, Venice, Italy, D187 (Box 153)
      - The Acropolis, Wall of Themistokles, Athens, Greece, D188 (Box 153)
      - The Forum (Elevation), Pompeii, D189 (Box 153)
      - Plan of the Forum, Pompeii, D190 (Box 153)
      - Factory Garden, Tokyo, Japan, D191 (Box 153)
      - Rathaus, Rothenburg, D192 (Box 153)
      - Slaughter House, Dresden, D193 (Box 153)
      - Malhasten (Artists' Club), Dusseldorf, D194 (Box 153)
      - Town Hall, Arlington, MA, D195 (Box 153)
      - Public Market, Madison, WI, D196 (Box 153)
      - Public Market, Madison, WI, D197 (Box 153)
      - John Woodcock Public School, North Attleboro, MA, D198 (Box 153)
      - Country School for Girls, Roland Park, Baltimore, D199 (Box 153)
      - The Square, Gardner, MA, D200 (Box 153)
      - Church, Biltmore, NC, December 1912; D201 (Box 154)
      - Church and Vestry Building, Biltmore, NC, 1913; D202 (Box 154)
      - Post Office, Biltmore, NC, D203 (Box 154)
      - Barber Shop, Biltmore, NC, D204 (Box 154)
      - St. Philip's Church, Charleston, SC, D205 (Box 154)
      - Plan for Capitol Grounds, Madison, WI, D206 (Box 154)
      - School Gardens, Letchworth, England, D207 (Box 154)
      - Factory Employees, Letchworth, England, D208 (Box 154)
      - Backs of Shops, Hampstead, England, D209 (Box 154)
      - Central Square, Hampstead, England - Plan, D210 (Box 154)
      - Shops & Apartments on Finckley Road, Hampstead, D211 (Box 154)
      - Village Hall, Panshanger, England, D212 (Box 154)
      - City Hall, Portland, ME, D213 (Box 154)
      - Civic Center Scheme, Portland, ME - Plan, D214 (Box 154)
      - City Hall Scheme, Portland, ME, D215 (Box 154)
      - City Hall (Proposed), Rochester, NY, D216 (Box 154)
      - Civic Center (Proposed), Rochester, NY, D217 (Box 154)
      - Queens College, Charlotte, NC - Plan, D218 (Box 154)
      - St. Michaels Church, Charleston, SC, D219 (Box 154)
      - Centre Market, Charleston, SC, D220 (Box 154)
      - Civic Center Sketch, Keokuk, IA, D221 (Box 154)
      - Keokuk Civic Center Plan, D222 (Box 154)
      - State Capitol, Little Rock, AR, D223 (Box 154)
      - San Diego Exposition, Sketch, D224 (Box 154)
      - Fire Escape, Merdem Shop Building, New York City, 1914; D225 (Box 154)
      - Civic Center, Sacramento, D226 (Box 154)
      - The Mansion House, Lord Mayor's Headquarters, Dublin, D228 (Box 154)
      - City Hall, Dublin, Ireland, D229 (Box 154)
      - Bank of Ireland, Dublin, Ireland, D230 (Box 154)
      - Trinity College, Dublin, Ireland, D231 (Box 154)
      - Trinity College & Bank of Ireland, Dublin, Ireland, D232 (Box 154)
      - The Four Courts, Dublin, D233 (Box 154)
      - Custom House, Dublin, D234 (Box 154)
      - Woolworth Building, New York City, D235 (Box 154)
      - City Theatre, Frankfurt, Germany, D236 (Box 154)
      - Municipal Slaughter House, Dresden, Germany, D237 (Box 154)
      - Municipal Gas Works, Frankfurt, Germany, D238 (Box 154)
      - Manufacturing Buildings, Dusseldorf, D239 (Box 154)
      - Civic Center Plan, Winchester, MA, D240 (Box 154)
      - Old City Hall & New Municipal Building, New York City, D241 (Box 154)
      - Country Life Press, New York City - Plan and Elevation, D242 (Box 154)
      - Plant of General Electric Co., Nela Park, (E) Cleveland, Ohio, D243 (Box 154)
      - Panama-Pacific Exposition, Night-View, D244 (Box 154)
      - The Bourse, Paris, D245 (Box 154)
      - Community Center Statement, Gary, IN, D246 (Box 154)
      - Statement, Froebel School, Gary, IN, D247 (Box 154)
      - General Statement, Froebel School, Gary, IN, D248 (Box 154)
      - Froebel School and Grounds, Gary, IN, D249 (Box 154)
      - Civic Center Plan, Sacramento, CA, D250 (Box 154)
      - General View, San Francisco Exposition, D251 (Box 155)
      - Lagoon & Fountain, So. Gardens, San Francisco Exposition, D252 (Box 155)
      - Tower of Jewels, Night Illumination, San Francisco Exposition, D253 (Box 155)
      - Court of the Ages, San Francisco Exposition, D254 (Box 155)
      - Palace of Fine Arts, San Francisco Exposition, D255 (Box 155)
      - Statue End of the Trail, San Francisco Exposition, D256 (Box 155)
      - Bird's Eye View, San Diego Exposition, D257 (Box 155)
      - The Prado, San Diego Exposition, D258 (Box 155)
      - California Tower, San Diego Exposition, D259 (Box 155)
      - Plaza de Panama, San Diego Exposition, D260 (Box 155)
      - Esplanade, San Diego Exposition, D261 (Box 155)
      - The Basin, San Diego Exposition, D262 (Box 155)
      - Botanical Garden, San Diego Exposition, D263 (Box 155)
      - Home Economy Building, San Diego Exposition, D264 (Box 155)
      - Civic Center, Calexico, CA, D265 (Box 155)
      - The Hotel, Atascadero Colony, CA, D266 (Box 155)
      - Department Store, Atascadero, So. California, D267 (Box 155)
      - Publishing Plant, Atascadero Colony, CA, D268 (Box 155)
      - Publicly-owned Theatres and Concert Halls in Europe, D269 (Box 155)
      - Post Office, Augusta, GA, D270 (Box 155)
      - General Plan, Froebel School & School Grounds, Gary, IN - Perspective, D271 (Box 155)
      - Mission, Santa Barbara, CA, D272 (Box 155)
      - Study for Civic Center, Little Rock, AR, D273 (Box 155)
      - Proposed Public Market, Erie, PA - Plan, D274 (Box 155)
      - Court of the Ages & Mulgardt Tower, San Francisco Exposition, D275 (Box 155)
      - Bell Telephone Building, Albany, D276 (Box 155)
      - D & H Building, Albany, NY, D277 (Box 155)
      - Home of La Prenza, Buenos Aires, D278 (Box 155)
      - Simmons Library & Lincoln Monument, Kenosha, WI, D279 (Box 155)
      - Proposed Civic Center, Bridgeport, CT, D280 (Box 155)
      - Proposed Education Group, Golden Hill, Bridgeport, CT, D281 (Box 155)
      - Community Headquarters, Santa Barbara, CA, D282 (Box 155)
      - Disapproved & Approved Design for Whitehall Ferry Terminal, New York, D283 (Box 155)
      - Civic Center, Cardiff, Wales - Geddes, D284 (Box 155)
      - Tower, Springfield, MA, D285 (Box 155)
      - High School, Showing planting, Madison, WI, D286 (Box 155)
      - Civic Center, Little Rock, AR - Plan, D287 (Box 155)
      - Old State House, Little Rock, AR, D288 (Box 155)
      - Union Station & Civic Center, Akron, OH, 1919; D289 (Box 155)
      - Common & Public Buildings, Niagara Falls, NY - Plan, D290 (Box 155)
      - City Hall in Group, Niagara Falls, Perspective, D291 (Box 155)
      - Band Stand, The Common, Niagara Falls, D292 (Box 155)
      - Studies for Building Groups, Flint, MI, D293 (Box 155)
      - War Memorial Study, La Crosse - Rendered Plan, D294 (Box 155)
      - North Side Community Center, La Crosse, WI, D295 (Box 155)
      - Village Green & Post Office, Chateaugay, NY, D296 (Box 155)
      - Colonnade & Post Office, Chateaugay, NY, D297 (Box 155)
      - Civic Center, Denver, 1919; D298 (Box 155)
      - Civic Center, San Francisco, D299 (Box 155)
      - Airplane View, Trafalgar Square, London, D300 (Box 155)
      - Street View, Civic Center, Bordeaux, France, D301 (Box 156)
      - The City Hall, Bordeaux, France, D302 (Box 156)
      - Community Center, Diagram, D303 (Box 156)
      - Campanile, Giotto, Florence, D304 (Box 156)
      - Ulm Cathedral Spire - Drawing by John Ruskin, D305 (Box 156)
      - Airplane View of Opera House, Paris, D306 (Box 156)
      - Civic Center & Chase Office Building, Waterbury, CT, D307 (Box 156)
      - Chase Office Building, Waterbury, CT, D308 (Box 156)
      - Bank Building, Bristol, CT, D309 (Box 156)
      - Store Center, Lake Forest, IL, D310 (Box 156)
      - Schoolhouse, Balboa Heights, C.Z. (Panama), D311 (Box 156)
      - United Fruit Office, Canal Zone, D312 (Box 156)
      - High School Site, Flint, MI, D313 (Box 156)
      - Town Hall, Weston, MA, D314 (Box 156)
      - Town Hall, Weston, MA, D315 (Box 156)
      - Proposed Town Hall, Watertown, MA, D316 (Box 156)
      - Hollins Institute, near Roanoke, VA, D317 (Box 156)
      - The Garden City Press, Long Island, NY, D318 (Box 156)
      - Town Hall, Arlington, MA, D319 (Box 156)
      - Proposed Building Group, Framingham, MA, D320 (Box 156)
      - Town Hall, Tewksbury, MA, D321 (Box 156)
      - American Optical Co., Southbridge, MA, D322 (Box 156)
      - Patio, Pan-American Building, Washington, DC, D323 (Box 156)
      - Public Buildings, Mirror Lake, St. Petersburg, FL, D324 (Box 156)
      - Post Office Arcade, St. Petersburg, FL, D325 (Box 156)
      - High School, Flint, MI, D326 (Box 156)
      - Civic Center, San Francisco, CA, D327 (Box 156)
      - Public School, Santa Barbara, CA, D328 (Box 156)
      - Airplane View, Massachusetts Institute of Technology, D329 (Box 156)
      - US Marine Corps Base, San Diego, D330 (Box 156)
      - Civic Center Plan, Columbus, GA, D331 (Box 156)
      - High School Plan, Columbus, GA, D332 (Box 156)
      - Cathedral of Learning, University of Pittsburgh, 1926; D333 (Box 156)
      - View, Exposition, San Diego, 1915; D334 (Box 156)
      - Exposition Plan, Balboa Park, San Diego, D335 (Box 156)
      - General View, Rolyat, St. Petersburg, FL, D336 (Box 156)
      - Hotel Alba, Palm Beach - Perspective, D337 (Box 156)
      - Public Library, Los Angeles, D338 (Box 156)
      - Stadthaus, Stockholm, Sweden, 1930; D339 (Box 156)
      - Proposed Civic Center, New York City, D340 (Box 156)
      - City Hall, San Diego, CA, D341 (Box 156)
      - Civic Center, San Francisco, CA, 1929; D342 (Box 156)
      - Civic Center, Denver, 1929; D343 (Box 156)
      - Civic Center, Auto Parking, Denver, D344 (Box 156)
      - Proposed City Hall, Buffalo, NY, 1927; D345 (Box 156)
      - State Capitol, Little Rock, AR - Proposal Plan, 1929; D346 (Box 156)
      - City Hall, Little Rock, AR, 1929; D347 (Box 156)
      - Block Opposite City Hall, Little Rock, 1929; D348 (Box 156)
      - Boston Custom House, Tower, from Water, D349 (Box 156)
      - Old Trinity Lutheran Church, Lancaster, PA, D350 (Box 156)
      - "Wheatland," Home of President Buchanan, Lancaster, PA, D351 (Box 157)
      - Town Common, Weston, MA - Before & After, D352 (Box 157)
      - Capitol, Lincoln, NE, D353 (Box 157)
      - Minor Open Spaces, Metropolitan Boston, E1 (Box 158)
      - South Framingham Square, Vista, E10 (Box 158)
      - "Common," Framingham, MA, E11 (Box 158)
      - Wayland Center, Approach, Wayland, MA, E12 (Box 158)
      - Wayland Center, As proposed, Wayland, MA, E13 (Box 158)
      - Oval, Billerica, MA - Before, E14 (Box 158)
      - Oval, Billerica, MA - After (3 years), E15 (Box 158)
      - "The Puritan" by St. Gaudens, Springfield, MA, E16 (Box 158)
      - City Hall Square, New York City, E17 (Box 158)
      - Unions Square, New York City, E18 (Box 158)
      - Sketch Design for Town Common, Montclair, NJ, E19 (Box 158)
      - Open Spaces & Public Buildings, Boston & Elsewhere, E2 (Box 158)
      - Town Centre, Design Sketch, Montclair, NJ, E20 (Box 158)
      - Plan of Town Center & Public Plaza, Montclair, NJ, E21 (Box 158)
      - Sketch Design for Business Centre Plaza, Montclair, NJ, E22 (Box 158)
      - Penn Square, Reading, PA, E23 (Box 158)
      - Penn Square, as Proposed, Reading, PA, E24 (Box 158)
      - Dupont Circle, Washington, DC, E25 (Box 158)
      - Fourteenth Street Circle, Washington, DC, E26 (Box 158)
      - Lafayette Square, Washington, DC, E27 (Box 158)
      - Washington Monument, Baltimore, E28 (Box 158)
      - "Elmwood" Park, Roanoke, VA, 1911; E29 (Box 158)
      - Small Open Spaces, Watertown & Brookline, MA, E3 (Box 158)
      - State St. Triangle, Madison, WI, E30 (Box 158)
      - Jefferson Square, San Francisco, E31 (Box 158)
      - City Square, called Central Park, Los Angeles, 1911; E32 (Box 158)
      - City Square (Central Park), Los Angeles, 1911; E33 (Box 158)
      - The Plaza, San Diego, E34 (Box 158)
      - Westmont Park, Montreal, Canada, E35 (Box 158)
      - Public Gardens, Halifax, E36 (Box 158)
      - Trafalgar Square, London, E37 (Box 158)
      - Trafalgar Square, London, E38 (Box 158)
      - Trafalgar Square, London, E39 (Box 158)
      - Harvard Square, Cambridge, MA, 1840; E4 (Box 158)
      - Trafalgar Square, just off Upper Oxford St., London, E40 (Box 158)
      - Trafalgar Square, from North Side, London, E41 (Box 158)
      - St. James Park, Home Guards Parade, London, E42 (Box 158)
      - Lincolns Mn Fields, London, E43 (Box 158)
      - London Poor. Temple Gardens, waiting for Gates to Open, E44 (Box 158)
      - Temple Gardens, London, E45 (Box 158)
      - St. James Church Yard, London, E46 (Box 158)
      - London Outcast use of Parks, E47 (Box 158)
      - Royal Exchange & Bank, London, E48 (Box 158)
      - Leicester Square, London, E49 (Box 158)
      - Harvard Square, Cambridge, MA, 1910; E5 (Box 158)
      - Plaza, Somerset, England, E50 (Box 158)
      - Trolley Waiting Shelters, Brookline, MA, E6 (Box 158)
      - Broadway Park, Brookline, MA, E7 (Box 158)
      - Lexington Common, 1905; E8 (Box 158)
      - Minute Man & Common, Lexington, MA, E9 (Box 158)
      - Flower Market, Piazza de Spagna, Rome, E100 (Box 159)
      - Market Cross, Salisbury, England, E51 (Box 159)
      - Market Place, East Retford, Nottinghamshire, England, E52 (Box 159)
      - Village Centre, Shere, Surrey, E53 (Box 159)
      - The "White House," Shere Surrey, E54 (Box 159)
      - Place de l'Opera, Paris, E55 (Box 159)
      - Place de la Concorde, Paris, E56 (Box 159)
      - Place Vendome & Columns, Paris, E57 (Box 159)
      - Place de la Bastille, Paris, E58 (Box 159)
      - Palais Royal, Paris, E59 (Box 159)
      - Place d'Italia, Paris, E60 (Box 159)
      - Place Stanislas, Nancy, France, E61 (Box 159)
      - Public Garden, Lisieux, France, E62 (Box 159)
      - Imperial Palace & List Garten, Berlin, Germany, E63 (Box 159)
      - Lustplatz, Berlin, E64 (Box 159)
      - Palace Square, Berlin, E65 (Box 159)
      - Opera Place, Berlin, E66 (Box 159)
      - Belle Alliance Plaz, Berlin, E67 (Box 159)
      - Sophia Charlotte Platz, Berlin, E68 (Box 159)
      - Small Park, Am. Lietzensee, Charlottenburg, Berlin, E69 (Box 159)
      - Corneliusplatzz, Dusseldorf, E70 (Box 159)
      - Corneliusplatzz, Dusseldorf, E71 (Box 159)
      - Post-Platz, Dresden, E72 (Box 159)
      - Open Space, Dresden, E73 (Box 159)
      - Zwinger, Dresden, E74 (Box 159)
      - Park Walk near the Zwinger, Dresden, E75 (Box 159)
      - Albert Platz, Dresden, E76 (Box 159)
      - Nurnberger Platz, Dresden, E77 (Box 159)
      - Munchener Platz, Dresden, E78 (Box 159)
      - Marktplatz, Schandau, near Dresden, E79 (Box 159)
      - Marktplatz, Schandau, near Dresden, E80 (Box 159)
      - Imperial Opera House Plaza, Leipzig, Germany, E81 (Box 159)
      - Gutenbergs Platz, Strassburg, Germany, E82 (Box 159)
      - Old Castle, Column of Peace, Stuttgart, E83 (Box 159)
      - Palm Gardens, Frankfurt, Germany, E84 (Box 159)
      - Hans Sachs Platz, Nuremberg, E85 (Box 159)
      - Open Space, Darmstadt, Germany, E86 (Box 159)
      - The Market-Place, Weimar, Germany, E87 (Box 159)
      - Marion Platz & Old Rathaus, Munchen, E88 (Box 159)
      - Open Place, near Feldherrnhalle, Munchen, E89 (Box 159)
      - Karlsplatz Memorial - Plan, E90 (Box 159)
      - Karlsplatz, Munich, E91 (Box 159)
      - Promenadeplatz, Munchen, E92 (Box 159)
      - Wittelsbacher Fountain, Munchen, E93 (Box 159)
      - H of Garten, Munchen, E94 (Box 159)
      - Piazza de San Marco, Venice, E95 (Box 159)
      - Piazza de San Marco, Venice, E96 (Box 159)
      - Piazza del Popolo, Rome, E97 (Box 159)
      - Piazza del Popolo & Pincian Hill, Rome, E98 (Box 159)
      - Piazza del Popolo, looking toward St. Peter's, Rome, E99 (Box 159)
      - Piazza of St. Peters, Rome, E101 (Box 160)
      - Piazza del Campidoglio, Rome, E102 (Box 160)
      - Piazza del Campidoglio, Rome, E103 (Box 160)
      - Piazza Municipio, Naples, E104 (Box 160)
      - La Place Neuve, Geneva, E105 (Box 160)
      - Grand Plaza, Madrid, Spain, E106 (Box 160)
      - Patio, Jockey Club, City of Mexico, E107 (Box 160)
      - Central Park (open space), Havana, Cuba, E108 (Box 160)
      - The Palace and Plaza, Cuba, E109 (Box 160)
      - Grove, Luxembourg, E110 (Box 160)
      - Fountain of Medici, Luxembourg, Paris, E111 (Box 160)
      - Luxembourg Gardens, Paris, E112 (Box 160)
      - Tuileries Garden, Paris, E113 (Box 160)
      - Tuileries Garden, Paris, E114 (Box 160)
      - Potsdamer Platz, Berlin, E115 (Box 160)
      - Rodergasse, Rothenberg, E116 (Box 160)
      - Kapuzinerplatz, Dinkelsbühl, Germany, E117 (Box 160)
      - Independence Square, Philadelphia, E118 (Box 160)
      - Place de la Concorde, Paris, E119 (Box 160)
      - Botanical Garden & Pavillion, Brussels, E120 (Box 160)
      - Pirnaischer Platz, Dresden, E121 (Box 160)
      - Panorama from Dreikonigskirche, Opera House in centre, Dresden, E122 (Box 160)
      - Tulips, Jones Square, Rochester, NY, E123 (Box 160)
      - Copley Square, As Proposed, Boston, 1912; E124 (Box 160)
      - Union Square, San Francisco, E125 (Box 160)
      - City Square, Charleston, SC, E126 (Box 160)
      - "Triangle," Bournville, England, E127 (Box 160)
      - Walpole, MA, Center - General Plan, E128 (Box 160)
      - East Walpole Center - Plan, E129 (Box 160)
      - South Walpole - Plan for Center, E130 (Box 160)
      - South Walpole, View of Center, E131 (Box 160)
      - Walpole Common, E132 (Box 160)
      - Maine Monument, Central Park, New York, E133 (Box 160)
      - Monument to Mr. Millet & A.W. Butt (Titanic), Washington, DC, E134 (Box 160)
      - US Grant Hotel & Plaza, San Diego, E135 (Box 160)
      - Exhibition Entrance, Dublin, 1914; E136 (Box 160)
      - Children's Fairy Fountain, Friedrichshain, Berlin, E137 (Box 160)
      - Castle Square, Karlsruhe, Germany, E138 (Box 160)
      - Monument Place, Indianapolis, E139 (Box 160)
      - Local Center, Sacramento, CA, E140 (Box 160)
      - Selection of Site, Civil War Monument, E141 (Box 160)
      - Memorial, Civil War, "The Horrors of War", E142 (Box 160)
      - War Memorial - Figure by R.N. Burnham, E143 (Box 160)
      - Airplane View, Place de la Concorde, Paris, E144 (Box 160)
      - Airplane View, Piazza del Popolo, Rome, E145 (Box 160)
      - McFarlan Park, Flint Department of Parks, 1921; E146 (Box 160)
      - The Common, Before & After, Cohasset, MA, E147 (Box 160)
      - Osceola Park, Belleair, FL - Sketch, E148 (Box 160)
      - Outdoor Theater, Belleair, FL - Sketch, E149 (Box 160)
      - Market Place, Delft Memorial, Holland, January 1925; E150 (Box 160)
      - Barbara, Orr's Island, F1 (Box 161)
      - "Mischief brewing," Playground needed, F10 (Box 161)
      - Playground cartoon, "Children as asset", F11 (Box 161)
      - Environment & Recreation, "What shall the Future be", F12 (Box 161)
      - The Contagion of Health, F13 (Box 161)
      - Storytelling on the Playground, F14 (Box 161)
      - Child Welfare, Louis Potter, F15 (Box 161)
      - Charlesbank Playground, "The Ground" Affair, F16 (Box 161)
      - Charlesbank, Boston - Before, F17 (Box 161)
      - Charlesbank - Plan, F18 (Box 161)
      - Children's Day, Franklin Park, Boston, F19 (Box 161)
      - Street boys gambling on Sunday morning, F2 (Box 161)
      - No title - people in park, F20 (Box 161)
      - Playstand, Franklin Park, Boston, F21 (Box 161)
      - No title - people at tennis courts, F22 (Box 161)
      - No title - children at play outdoors, F23 (Box 161)
      - Beach Playground, Savin Hill, Boston, F24 (Box 161)
      - Columbus Ave. Playground, Boston, F25 (Box 161)
      - Playground, Apparatus, F26 (Box 161)
      - Playground, San Box, Columbus Ave., F27 (Box 161)
      - School Playground, F28 (Box 161)
      - Private Playground, Mr. Joseph Lee, F29 (Box 161)
      - Charles of an Earlier Day, F3 (Box 161)
      - Private Playground, Boston, Joseph Lee, F30 (Box 161)
      - Private Playground, Boston, Joseph Lee, F31 (Box 161)
      - Playground Referendum, F32 (Box 161)
      - Baseball on Cambridge, MA Common, F33 (Box 161)
      - Site of Cambridge Field, 1894; F34 (Box 161)
      - Cambridge Field, 1896; F35 (Box 161)
      - Cambridge Field - Plan, F36 (Box 161)
      - Sand Lawns, Cambridge Field, F37 (Box 161)
      - Skating, Cambridge Field, F38 (Box 161)
      - Shelter, Cambridge Field, F39 (Box 161)
      - "Pitching Pennies", F4 (Box 161)
      - Sand Gardens, Broadway Park, Cambridge, F40 (Box 161)
      - Ridge Field, Cambridge - Plan, F41 (Box 161)
      - The Mill Pond, Cambridge, F42 (Box 161)
      - Coasting, Avon Hill, Cambridge, 1909; F43 (Box 161)
      - Dime Museum, Cambridge, F44 (Box 161)
      - Public Gym, exterior, Brookline, MA, F45 (Box 161)
      - Municipal Gym, interior, Brookline, MA, F46 (Box 161)
      - Public Baths, exterior, Brookline, F47 (Box 161)
      - Public Baths, interior, Brookline, F48 (Box 161)
      - Public Baths, Brookline - Plan, F49 (Box 161)
      - "Boys Wanted", F5 (Box 161)
      - Town Field, Belmont - Athletic House built by High School boys, F50 (Box 161)
      - Wordsworth, "Boy of Winander", F6 (Box 161)
      - The People at Play, F7 (Box 161)
      - The People at Play - Duplicate, F7 (Box 161)
      - Greek Training of Children, F8 (Box 161)
      - Training of Body, Mind, and Soul - Chinese children at dumb bell exercise, F9 (Box 161)
      - Restaurant, Chicago Park System, F100 (Box 162)
      - Stoneham Playground - Preliminary Plan, F51 (Box 162)
      - Field House, Stoneham Playground, F52 (Box 162)
      - Kindergarten, Oakdale School, Dedham, MA, F53 (Box 162)
      - Playgrounds & Churches - Moxom, Springfield, MA, F54 (Box 162)
      - Davis Park Playground, Providence, RI, F55 (Box 162)
      - Tennis Courts, Pope Park, Hartford, CT, F56 (Box 162)
      - Riverside Park, School Gardens, Hartford, CT, F57 (Box 162)
      - Toy Boats, Central Park, NY, 1908; F58 (Box 162)
      - Play Festival, New York City, 1908; F59 (Box 162)
      - Play Festival, New York City, F60 (Box 162)
      - Play Festival, New York City, F61 (Box 162)
      - 20-story playground, Proposed, New York City, F62 (Box 162)
      - Roof Playground, New York City, F63 (Box 162)
      - Boy life in New York City, F64 (Box 162)
      - Juvenile Court Waiting Room, Boys herded by the dozen, Brooklyn, F65 (Box 162)
      - Juvenile Court, Judge Wilhen, Personal Conference, Brooklyn, F66 (Box 162)
      - Girls in Court, Waiting to be called, Brooklyn, F67 (Box 162)
      - The Juvenile Court, F68 (Box 162)
      - Outdoor Gym, Crotona Park, New York, F69 (Box 162)
      - Crotona Park, Playground, New York, F70 (Box 162)
      - Wading Pool, Watertown, NY, F71 (Box 162)
      - Wading Pool, West Side Park, Newark, F72 (Box 162)
      - Playground, Newark, NJ, F73 (Box 162)
      - Teeter Board, Newark, NJ, F74 (Box 162)
      - Playground, East Orange, NJ, F75 (Box 162)
      - School Playground, Maple Ave., Montclair, NJ, F76 (Box 162)
      - Fairmount Park, Richard Smith Memorial Playground, F77 (Box 162)
      - 100 yard dash, Institute for Blind, Overbrook,PA, F78 (Box 162)
      - Garden work, Institute for the Blind, Overbrook, PA, F79 (Box 162)
      - Throwing the hammer, Institute for Blind, Overbrook, PA, F80 (Box 162)
      - Dime Museum, Reading, PA, F81 (Box 162)
      - School Gardens, Reading, PA, F82 (Box 162)
      - Washington Playgrounds - Plan, F83 (Box 162)
      - May Day, Biltmore, NC, 1906; F84 (Box 162)
      - Boys playing on lot, Charlotte, NC, F85 (Box 162)